( grand orchestral fanfare playing )
MARK : Caitlyn , this is a process , okay ?
But it 's important for you to remember
that the only person who can save us is ourselves .
CAITLYN : He 's a monster .
A goddamn fucking monster .
That 's what he is .
( heavy , shuddering breaths )
But I can 't seem to get away from him .
Do you remember what drew you to Mitch in the first place ?
We met at work , and
he was charming and mysterious .
He wined and dined me and took me traveling ,
and ...
he told me it was me and him against the world .
He made me feel important .
RENFIELD : Hello .
My name is Robert Montague Renfield .
And just like all these decent folks ,
I am in a destructive relationship .
♪ ♪
- ( neck snaps ) - ( yells )
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa . That was a lot .
Maybe we should just back up to the beginning .
( thunder crashes )
Mr. Renfield , I bid you welcome .
I am ...
- Dracula . - ( wolf howls in distance )
RENFIELD : When I met him , I was a real estate lawyer
hoping to make a deal that would change my life
and my family 's lives forever .
Oh , and it most certainly did .
You will make a very good assistant , Mr. Renfield .
RENFIELD : I understand how Caitlyn feels .
I never drink wine .
RENFIELD : He also wined and dined me .
He made me feel important .
He introduced me into high society .
- We went to the theater . - ( applause )
- We traveled to exotic places . - ( people screaming )
And then he made me his familiar .
Which means that I take care of Master 's every need .
Including staff changes
and arranging his special dietary requirements .
( bite crunches )
Look , I didn 't just jump into serving the Prince of Darkness .
We had some great times .
But just like all great times ...
- DRACULA : Servant . - ... they come to an end .
DRACULA : The hunters have returned .
( grunts )
RENFIELD : Ah , yes .
The bugs . This comes up a lot .
Dracula 's powers come from consuming human life .
Mine come from eating bugs .
Make sense ? Great . Now , where were we ?
- ( yells ) - ( screams )
- ( speaking Latin ) - ( snarling )
- ( growls ) - I 'm coming , Master !
Shit . Fuck . Shit .
Shit . Fuck . Shit . Fuck .
- ( whooshing ) - ( grunting )
Sh-Sh-Sh-Shit .
This is a protection circle , Renfield .
Mm .
He cannot escape .
Let us rid this world of his evil ,
and you can finally be free !
DRACULA : Free ? ( scoffs )
The moment I 'm gone ,
they will lock you away for what you 've done for me .
I am your only salvation .
I am your only friend .
I am the only one
who cares for you .
RENFIELD : I actually remember thinking ,
" He really , really means it this time . "
( whooshing )
PRIEST : Renfield !
We are the last of our kind .
From now on , every drop of blood Dracula spills
will be on your hands .
( hisses , roars )
RENFIELD : Fuck . I was not expecting that .
( screams )
Or that .
( screaming )
( coughing )
Master , you okay ?
No .
Yeah .
This is a fairly typical result .
At the peak of his powers , Dracula goes on
a full-tilt blood-sucking bender ,
the good guys show up and do their thing ,
and then it 's up to me to clean up the mess .
- ( thunder rumbling ) - It 's what I call our transitional period .
So I take him to a new city , nurse him back to full power ,
find a decent place to ride it out
until the whole cycle starts all over again .
Uh , excuse me . H-Hi .
May I borrow a pen , please ?
Thank ... you .
Which brings us back here .
In the meantime , I come here and listen to these poor souls
talk about their monsters .
You were just talking about Mitch , what ...
I know this is , like , way down the list of bad stuff ,
but he 's also really into ska .
- The kind of music ? - Yes .
Fishbone , Mustard Plug , Voodoo Glow Skulls .
I fucking hate that shit !
I 'm so sorry , Caitlyn . I 'm so ...
- Mark , I am ... I 'm so sorry . - MARK : It 's okay .
Is that the one that 's 99 % horns ?
Yeah , see , that 's what I was thinking .
No . That 's a huge oversimplification
of ska 's innovative contribution to music .
( crying ) : Oh , my God , who am I ?
( coughing )
- Renfield ? - Hmm ?
Sorry , no , I swallowed a bug .
Unintentionally .
What-what other way is there to ...
Would you like to share your story ?
No . Thank-thank you . I don 't think you 'd understand .
I know it 's scary .
And you think things are never gonna change ,
but I promise you , one day you 're gonna realize
that you can have the life that you want .
But in the meantime , I just hope
that you get something out of coming here .
I am .
That 's great .
RENFIELD : Oh , yes , I 'm getting something
out of coming here : victims .
But not these victims .
MARK : Let 's do our affirmations .
( inhaling deeply )
GROUP : I am enough , and I have enough .
I deserve happiness .
I am grateful for all that I am ,
and I take full charge of my life today .
RENFIELD : They can repeat these
- affirmations all they want . - ( applause )
It 'll never make their problems go away .
But I can .
Now , no one 's ever gonna call me a hero ,
but I 've come up with a mutually beneficial solution
for people like Caitlyn :
get rid of their monsters by giving mine what he needs .
( " The Same Everyday " by The Slackers playing )
Hey , Doug . What are you doing over there , buddy ?
There 's somebody out there , Mitch .
Oh , my God , there 's no one out there , Doug !
Bro , do you think the Lobo family is gonna
let us get away with this ?
We stole their fucking drugs , man .
I don 't want to hear it , Doug !
( music stops )
Goddamn it .
- What the fuck ? - Oh , fuck .
That was the best part .
What the fuck , man ?
This is exactly why you never set your picnic up
next to a pile of dog ...
Shit ! Okay .
Hello , Mitch .
Uh , look .
Wait , wait , wait !
Okay , hold on . I 'm-I 'm sorry .
Okay ? I 'm sorry .
It 's too late for sorrys .
You took something you can never give back .
Well , we can give it back . That 's not a problem .
We 'll just give it all back to you . There it is .
Go ahead .
- Have it . No problem . - RENFIELD : Uh ...
- what is this ? - DOUG : It 's the , um ...
th-the drugs we stole from your boss , sir .
I 'm sorry .
Uh , who do you think I am ?
A-A hit man sent to kill us .
( chuckling )
RENFIELD : I am something much ,
much worse .
I 'm a friend of Caitlyn .
( laughter )
( laughing ) : Oh , my God .
Get the fuck out of here . No , no !
( Bizet 's " Carmen Suite No. 2 : II . Habanera " playing )
( grunting and groaning )
( muffled shouting )
( muffled squealing )
( sighs )
( muffled grunt )
( muffled shouting )
Wait . What did you say about a hit man sent to kill you ?
Oh .
( deep voice ) : Who are you ?
A friend of Caitlyn 's .
Uh , more of an acquaintance .
You were smaller from back there .
Funny .
Oh ! ( grunts )
( grunting )
Looks like you 're out of knives .
- ( blade slashes ) - ( grunts )
( gasping ) : I was wrong .
( whimpering )
( growling )
( engine revving )
( sniffs ) Ah .
Yeah , of course the hit is going well .
I got Apache Joe on it .
( scoffs ) The man cuts out people 's tongues
with a hunting knife .
You tell him his name is racist .
- ( grunts ) - ( whimpers )
- Come on ! - ( horn honking )
( grunts )
( groans )
( whimpers )
( grunting , panting )
( roars )
( sighs )
Oh , shit .
RENFIELD : Oh , shit .
Shit .
What the fuck ? !
( groaning )
( tires squealing )
♪ ♪
You , uh , been drinking tonight , sir ?
No .
Why ? You interested ?
All right , get the hell out of here .
Everything okay over here , partner ?
Yes .
Just frustrating being on this shit detail
when there 's real crimes happening out there .
( chuckles ) : Drunk driving isn 't real crime ?
You know what I mean , Chris .
We got a stack of missing person reports to follow up on .
( engine revving , tires squealing )
- ( horn honking ) - TEDDY : Come on !
- Holy shit , it 's Teddy Lobo . - What the fuck ? Come on !
- Are you sure ? - You know who I am ?
I 'm Teddy fucking Lobo !
Yeah , I 'm pretty sure .
Don 't do anything crazy , Rebecca .
I 'm just doing my job .
You do your job in a very crazy way ,
especially when it comes to the Lobos .
Fuck .
Oh , fuck .
- Fuck it ! - ( engine revving )
Look out , Chris !
Fuck a dick ! Shit !
Don 't move ! Hands on the wheel !
I got a prescription for this shit !
Shit .
What did I fucking do ?
- Is he throwing drugs at us ? - Yes !
I didn 't do anything wrong .
Fuck . Cocaine !
You can 't fucking catch ...
Are you fucking serious ?
( grunts )
( yelps , groans )
( siren wailing in distance )
You 're under arrest , bitch .
( sighs ) : Fuck .
RENFIELD : After decades of being
chased away from every corner of the globe ,
our options and bank account have become a little limited .
It 's not exactly a castle ,
but it is exactly the kind of place
no one tends to notice a convalescing monster .
( straining )
Master ?
Master .
( panting , grunting )
Oh , dear Jesus .
Master . ( chuckles )
There you are .
You 're looking
much better ?
Fetch me the hand .
Yes . Right away .
There you go . A little amuse-bouche .
Palate cleanser .
- ( grunts ) - Ugh .
Is that good ?
( retching )
What is this ?
Uh , that ...
Uh , that is , uh ... that 's Doug , I believe .
Doug is trash !
You 're feeding me trash !
I 'm sorry , Master .
This one doesn 't even have a head .
Oh , no , he did have a head .
You know , I don 't ask for much , Renfield .
Just the blood of a few dozen innocent people .
I know . I 'm sorry , Master .
Let 's-let 's get you sat down , and then ...
I want happy couples , unsuspecting tourists ,
a handful of nuns , a-a ... a busload of cheerleaders .
A busload of cheerleaders ?
A busload of cheerleaders
will get me back to full power like that .
Do you mean female cheerleaders ?
Don 't make it a sexual thing .
No , no . I did not say it was .
You know it 's not the gender I 'm concerned with .
You know , I-I 'll eat boys , I 'll eat girls .
It 's the purity .
It alone will bring me back to ...
Full power .
I get it , Master .
You deserve better .
But the modern world is a dangerous place .
Maybe if we were just a little bit more careful ,
we could , you know , stop running .
You know , settle down , and I could have ...
We could have a life again .
( grunts )
It must be difficult
to be caught between their rules and mine .
( groaning )
Their rules offer a confusing tangle of morality ,
whereas mine are very simple .
You can kill and eat
whatever you want and never die .
And it truly is a gift .
And yet , you seem to think it makes you
some sort of a monster .
Do you have any idea how inconsiderate that is ?
( crying ) : I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry .
My needs are the only thing that matters , servant .
And what exactly are my needs ?
Um , your needs , your needs were the , uh ...
uh , happy couples , u-unsuspecting tourists , uh ...
nuns , nuns and a-a busload of cheerleaders .
Indeed .
RENFIELD : I suppose this is what you 'd call my health-care plan .
His blood has the power to heal the injured .
And there 's not even a copay .
Unless you consider my soul .
DRACULA : You will get me exactly what I want .
TEDDY : I cannot go to jail .
I 'll tell you anything you want to know .
What do you want to know ?
Murders ! Murders .
We fucking murdered so many fucking people in cold blood .
Like last night , for example , we murdered these people
for trying to steal our drugs .
That 's a twofer , my man . That is a fucking twofer .
Nobody 's been in the room yet , and he 's already confessing .
You see that ?
I 'm gonna take down the entire fucking Lobo empire
off of one traffic stop .
Put her there , partner .
- Let 's go . - What ?
- Let 's go . - I 'm out ?
- REBECCA : No . No ! - Let 's go .
- I didn 't say a fucking thing , by the way . - What the f ...
- I 'm out , baby ! - What the fuck is this ?
Excuse me , everybody . Guess what .
Fuck you !
Fuck you and you .
Hey . Hey , hey , hey , hey , hey . What is this ?
He was about to give up everything .
He was ready to say anything
because of the trauma you put him through .
He was already traumatized when I found him .
For crying out loud , Quincy .
- ( stammers ) - Your job is to bust drunk drivers ,
not single-handedly bring down the mob .
He was running from something , sir .
And then he crashed into a DUI checkpoint ,
committed ten felonies ,
and not to mention eff-you-ing a room full of cops .
- You eff-you me all the time . - Fuck you , Kyle !
Look , Quincy .
Your father was one of the most honest
and incorruptible cops I knew .
And you 're a lot like him .
And before he passed , I promised your father that
I would do my best to take care of you .
But sometimes , you got to know when to play ball .
This ain 't your stepping stone .
It 's your rock bottom .
What the fuck are you guys looking at , huh ?
( grunts in frustration )
Shit .
What 'd you do this time ?
What I do every time .
Catch Teddy Lobo committing a crime , and then :
What ? Oh , surprise , he got away with it again .
And what about your-your little FBI , uh , task force up there ?
You guys been back for four months .
What have you done about the Lobos ?
Oh , oh , oh , a-a wiretap ?
Subpoena ? A fucking parking ticket ?
A hard stare across a diner ?
I am just as mad about what they did to Dad as you are .
I want revenge just as bad as you do .
But every day , I force myself to swallow that anger
so I don 't fuck up my investigation .
And if you cannot learn to let that go
you 're never gonna get the justice that you want .
You 're not the only one who lost a dad here .
♪ Murder , murder , murder ♪
♪ When he bust in ♪
♪ When he bust in ... ♪
Here you go . Take care of yourself .
- You earned it . Shower yourself in it . - ( gasps ) Thanks .
- Teddy . - WOMAN : Ooh ! Okay .
Your mother wants to see you .
TEDDY : All right .
♪ Murder , murder , murder , when he bust in ♪
♪ Murder , murder , murder ... ♪
Downstairs .
♪ You might 've heard of him , the guy lost his nerve . ♪
♪ ♪
Long , even strokes .
Hey , Mom .
Teddy .
You said you want ... You said you wanted to see me ?
Take a seat , please .
Do you even know why we became
the most powerful crime family in this city ?
We 're not the biggest . We 're not the richest .
However , we are the most feared .
Our reputation for ruthlessness and violence
is something I have worked very hard to cultivate .
But lately , our enemies don 't seem to be
as afraid as they used to be .
( chuckling ) : They 're fucking scared , Mom .
Not the two-bit punks stealing our drugs .
Not the five families .
And not that fucking traffic cop .
This family is an empire , Teddy .
I built an empire .
And I need to know its future is secure .
I need to know whose hands it belongs in .
And I need to know those hands can get a little dirty .
REBECCA : I know Teddy 's up to something .
I 'm gonna find the evidence to make it stick .
Got a lot of orange paint .
What is that ? Some kind of warning ?
I think it 's lyrics to a ska song .
Ska 's not dead .
Fuck .
( " A Shot in the Night " by 1933 playing inside )
♪ You can touch the sky ♪
- ( lively chatter ) - ♪ ' Cause there 's a shot ♪
♪ In the night ♪
♪ Turning darkness into light ... ♪
RENFIELD : Oh , you 've got to be kidding me .
( horn honking )
( cheerleaders hollering )
Yeah ! All right !
You think you 'll get answers here ?
I think we 'll get dinner .
Maybe answers for dessert .
RONNIE : There she is .
You sure you want to do this , Teddy ?
TEDDY : Yes , I am sure I want to do this .
That cop needs to be reminded who runs this town .
( lively chatter , hollering )
♪ ♪
Oh , shit .
Fuck .
Oh , this is not a good look .
Not a good look at all . Abort . Abort .
Can you order me a number three ?
The toilet just ordered a number two .
( tires squealing )
Sorry .
♪ ♪
RENFIELD : Who the fuck are these guys ?
( whimpers )
( people screaming )
( indistinct shouting )
Move , and I 'll blow your fucking head off .
- Take that , tourist ! - ( screaming )
TEDDY : Get down !
Hey , do me a favor .
Just remain calm ,
and almost nobody will get hurt .
Thank you , Teddy .
I came here to connect you to a crime scene ,
and you go and turn it into one .
TEDDY : What you trying to do ?
Holy shit , were you trying to imitate your dad ?
What do you think , your dad died some brave hero ?
We beat the shit out of your father .
And while he was lying there on the floor ,
he begged for his life .
Your dad was a coward .
But you know what ? I want to save you that embarrassment .
I 'm gonna give you the chance to live .
All you have to do is admit to everybody here
that we own you , too .
So , what 's it gonna be ?
Shoot me .
What ?
You heard me , asshole .
Shoot me .
Shoot me like you shot my dad .
Or was that not you ?
Were you waiting in the car
while one of your boys did it for you ?
I 'm more than happy to do it , Teddy .
Shut the fuck up .
Have you ever shot someone before ?
TEDDY : I 've shot a million fucking people .
REBECCA : Then add me to the list .
Come on , tough guy . Shoot me .
TEDDY : If you think this is a fucking game ,
I will shoot you in your fucking face .
- REBECCA : Yeah ? Dare you . - ( insects buzzing )
TEDDY : You want to be a fucking hero right now ?
Okay , fine .
Here we go .
Congratulations .
You 're better than your father .
( grunting , yelling )
( pained yelling )
( screams )
- ( grunts ) - ( screams )
- ( man yells ) - ( gasps )
( man yells )
Fuck ! Shit !
( gasps )
( men screaming )
( panting )
- ( man groans ) - Oh .
- ( gunshot ) - ( man groans , body thuds )
RENFIELD : Are you okay ?
Yeah . Yeah . Oh ...
That was amazing . You were amazing .
What you did .
You stood up to him .
How did you do that ?
What kind of life would I lead
under the thumb of one of those assholes ?
A very ... a very sad one .
Yeah .
Did I watch you cut a guy 's arms off
with a decorative serving platter ?
Oh , uh , y-yeah .
That was adrenaline .
Uh , it was awesome .
( chuckles softly )
Um , I-I 'm-I 'm Rebecca Quincy .
Officer ... Officer Quincy .
Robert Montague Renfield .
Oh , uh , Montague . Cool .
Are you from around here or ...
Oh , no . I 'm ...
Uh , everywhere .
Ah , military .
That-that would explain all the moves .
Yeah , but forever ago - - the Great War .
Uh ... Iraq .
Maybe not great , uh , you know ,
but overall pretty good - - three out of five stars .
WOMAN : I 'm sorry .
I don 't mean to interrupt whatever this is ,
but ...
can we get up now ?
Uh , yeah .
If I could have everyone please , uh ,
just line up for me for witness statements .
And if we could all thank Mr. Renfield
for his brave , uh , efforts today .
GROUP : Thank you , Mr. Renfield .
MAN : You are the man , Mr. Renfield .
And , um , thank you .
Y-You ... you saved my life .
I ...
saved a life ?
You saved all our lives .
You must really not be from around here ,
' cause we certainly don 't see your kind very often .
I 'm sorry , what kind is that ?
Heroes .
Hmm .
RENFIELD : Wow . That was amazing .
She is amazing .
And she saw me .
She really saw me .
That hasn 't happened in ages .
I 'd forgotten what it feels like .
- Maybe there is hope . - Oh , God bless you .
Maybe she can ...
Renfield .
What are you doing ?
Get here now .
RENFIELD : Ah , fuck .
Do you think it 's too late to grab one of those nuns ?
What did we talk about yesterday ?
U-Um ...
I 've been up all day thinking about it .
Oh . What 's this ?
Ah . My plan .
RENFIELD : Your plan ?
But your plan has always been to just drink blood .
Exactly .
What have I been doing all these years ?
I mean , look at me , lurking in the shadows and filth
like some kind of a diseased animal .
You said it yourself - - I deserve better .
So , why am I not embracing what I truly am ?
Which is ?
A god , Renfield .
An immortal , insatiable - -
whoo ! - - all-powerful being .
Everything you said about the modern world is true .
- It is a dangerous place . - Hmm .
Only not for us .
For them , it 's a dangerous , sad , broken place
full of fear and desperation .
It 's weak .
Longing for a powerful force to guide it ,
control it , dominate it .
- Like you . - Hmm . ( chuckles )
I mean , this entire society was designed by Renfields ,
for Renfields .
So , why should I have to adapt to it ?
It should have to adapt to me .
( chuckling )
- I owe it all to you , servant . - Oh , no .
I think you actually might have read between the lines
- a little bit there . - Indeed .
We 're in this together ,
Dracula and Renfield .
From now on , humanity will no longer be divided
by the good and the evil ,
only by followers ...
and food .
( slurping )
You and I forever , until the end of time .
Bloody hell .
CAROL : How is my life ?
My life is like a ...
never-ending hallway of fun house mirrors , but ...
all the clowns are me .
Uh , hey , everyone .
I need your help .
Are you okay ?
RENFIELD : No .
I need to get out of a toxic relationship .
Okay . Well , well , well , well , take a seat and let her rip .
Okay , thanks .
Okay , yeah . Fuck Carol , I guess .
It 's ...
I hate her , too .
MARK : Why don 't you start by telling us
what brought you here in the first place .
I was on the job .
Uh , for my boss .
Uh , well , and I was actually following Bob ,
because I thought that Bob would make
a very good , um , uh ...
Friend ?
Yes . Thank you , Bob .
Thank you , Renfield .
And then , you know , I started to hear
all of your stories and ...
I mean , they were all so sad .
( laughter )
That 's us .
And , you know , for the first time in years ,
I felt like I wasn 't alone .
- You realized you 're a codependent . - Mm-hmm .
I need to change . I can see that I-I need to change ,
and , uh , I want to , but my boss ,
he 's pretty delusional , I think .
Uh , he thinks he can take over the world .
- ( light laughter ) - He 's a narcissist , Renfield .
We all know exactly how you feel .
- Yes . - Exactly .
No , he 's different .
- You can 't get him out of your head . - No .
Ooh , and you feel like he could kill you
with the snap of his fingers .
- Yes . Wouldn 't even need to snap . - Oh .
He controls rats with his mind .
Uh ...
It 's okay , it 's okay . He 's on medication .
Renfield , this is codependency 101 .
A narcissist will take full advantage
of a codependent 's low self-esteem ,
but you 're the one with the real power .
And all you got to do is take it back .
How do I do that ?
Focus on your needs .
I mean , I just haven 't thought about
any of my needs in years .
But if you were to stop focusing on his needs , what would happen ?
If I don 't ...
Yeah , what would happen ?
Stop focusing on his needs .
What would happen ?
- He won 't grow to full power . - ( encouraging chatter )
Exactly . He won 't grow to full power .
What ? That 's so weird .
Why would you phrase it like that ?
But yes , he 's right .
He 's absolutely right .
He won 't grow to full power .
You can take all that energy you 've spent on him
and put it toward yourself .
And then you will be the one who grows to full power .
- WOMAN : Yes . - MAN : Full power .
Me grow ... I-I 'm gonna grow to full power ?
I want to hear you say it .
Say , " I 'm gonna grow to full power . "
I-I-I 'm gonna grow to full power .
I heard you say it , but I didn 't believe you .
- Nope . - Let me hear you say it again .
- I 'm gonna grow to full power . - GROUP : Yes !
I see a smile there because you like it .
Now , say it like the world needs to hear it .
I 'm gonna grow to full power .
There you go !
( encouraging chatter , applause )
- Yes ! ( laughs ) - MARK : That guy who walks
in here every single week , say goodbye to him .
This is the person you are now .
♪ Oh , oh , oh , am I ready ? ♪
♪ Girl , there ain 't a doubt ♪
♪ Am I ready ? ♪
- ♪ What you talkin ' ' bout ? ♪ - ♪ Am I ready ? ♪
♪ You gon ' figure it out ♪
♪ To be loved , to be loved ♪
♪ You found me , I was fed up with the fantasy ♪
♪ What you wanna do ... ♪
Here you go .
The power is in your hands .
That book is your armor .
It 's your weapon . It 's your Bible .
That 's a cool ant farm . ( chuckles )
Is there room for one more ?
- Yeah . - Yeah ?
Thank you .
( buzzing )
MARK : Let 's give him some ideas .
Do you know what a brush is ?
- ♪ Am I ready ? ♪ - ♪ Girl , there ain 't a doubt ♪
Oh , and clean them nasty fingernails .
- ♪ What you talkin ' ' bout ? ♪ - ♪ Am I ready ? ♪
Spa day . I 'll go with you .
♪ To be loved ... ♪
Get your chakras balanced , homes .
TREVANTE : Ooh , and update that wardrobe to this century .
- ♪ Am I ready ? ♪ - ( song ends )
REBECCA : You would think that attacking a police officer
in front of a bunch of witnesses
at a restaurant would be enough to put Teddy Lobo behind bars .
You guys don 't think I know what 's going on here , huh ?
I don 't know how many of you assholes
are on the Lobos ' payroll ,
but there 's only so much evidence you can tamper with
and so many witnesses you can intimidate .
All right ? Because eventually ,
someone brave enough is going to step forward ,
and they 're going to help me take down the Lobos
and all of you motherfuckers !
Permanently ! Permanently !
( Renfield clears throat )
Mr. Renfield ?
Robert Montague Renfield , yes , at your service .
You look different .
- Oh . - Good different .
I really like your sweater .
Oh , thank you . ( chuckles )
- I went to Macy 's . - Oh .
Um , I 'm here to give my witness statement .
You always bring flowers to give a witness statement ?
Yeah , uh , well , th-they 're for everyone .
- They 're for everyone . - Everyone .
Do you , um ... Probably put it in some water .
And the rest are for you .
- Thank you . - Yeah . Pleasure .
Rebecca , is this your boyfriend ?
Shut the fuck up , Kyle !
Thank you for coming in , Mr. Renfield .
It really means a lot .
Yeah , it means a lot that I can actually
do the right thing , for once .
Well , if I could just stress how appreciative I am
that you 're here , uh , because without you ,
- I think I 'd be a bit lost . - No .
You stood up for everyone who 's ever lived in fear
of the powerful forces shaping their lives .
Okay ? And you need to keep doing that ,
because when people like you stop
standing up to people like them ,
that 's when the monsters take over .
So ... ( sighs )
You are not lost .
You 're an inspiration .
Thank you , Mr. Renfield .
It 's Robert .
Robert . ( chuckles )
BELLAFRANCESCA : This is the same prick
who took out everyone in the restaurant .
Who does he work for ?
- The five fucking families ? - TEDDY : I-I don 't know .
But we 've hacked into the NSA 's Eye in the Sky ,
and we can track him
using all these other cameras throughout the city .
Yes , I can get you access to whatever you want .
TEDDY : Yeah , and then we enhance .
- IT GUY : We got a trace on him . - TEDDY : Boom !
We did it . Now we can track his every move .
IT GUY : His last known location is at the old charity hospital .
You have until the end of the day to find him and kill him .
Give me ten minutes .
I 'll take the end of the day .
Can you run the DNA on this pen through the Bureau 's database ?
And Interpol .
I can 't trust this with anyone who works in my department .
This pen was found near a location
where these three guys went missing .
Teddy Lobo was fleeing from the same location
when I arrested him .
Huh .
Word on the street is these are the three guys
who allegedly stole drugs from the Lobos .
Right .
And the DNA evidence on this pen
just might connect Teddy Lobo to that crime scene .
Maybe it 's a long shot , but I got to try .
Look , I know I-I haven 't handled anything well
since Dad , um ...
but I really need your help .
Can you run this pen ?
Please .
♪ ♪
Let 's go . Come on .
( hushed ) : What the fuck ?
( faint squeaking )
( wings fluttering )
- ( bat squeaks ) - ( gasping )
( insects buzzing )
( grunts )
( panting )
Holy fucking shit .
Ronnie , call my mom !
I 'm on it .
TEDDY : Ronnie , call my fucking mom !
( men yelping , grunting )
Hello , Ronnie ?
( grunts )
Ronnie , is this another butt dial ?
Did you guys fucking bail ? Hello ?
- Guys ? - BELLAFRANCESCA : Teddy .
- What the fuck ? Mom . - Teddy .
Mom ?
Teddy ?
TEDDY : Do you know who the fuck I am ?
- Teddy ? - I 'm Teddy fucking Lobo .
- I am Count Dracula . - ( Teddy choking )
You win .
Who are you ?
You were sent by the church ?
Church ? No .
What are you fucking talking about ?
I 'm a criminal .
My whole organization is about evil .
Evil . Oh , fuck .
Dude .
Why are you here ?
I 'm here because I want to find this guy !
I 'm trying to find this guy .
He stuck his nose in our family business
and killed some of our guys
trying to save a bunch of innocent people .
So , what is he , like , your fucking roommate ?
He 's my servant .
He doesn 't seem to be serving you very well .
( grunts )
( bats squeaking )
REBECCA ( recorded ) : You 've reached Officer Quincy .
Please state your emergency at the sound of the beep .
- ( beep ) - RENFIELD : Uh , hi , Rebecca .
It 's not an emergency . It-it 's me , Robert .
What , uh , I was trying to ask was , um ,
maybe you 'd like to get a bite to eat ...
Hello , Renfield .
I 've been expecting you .
Please , come in .
Close the door .
Shit .
Marvelous attire .
Very colorful .
You look like the sort of boy who has to fight ' em off .
( laughs )
So , I suppose that 's a no
as to you bringing me my dinner tonight , hmm ?
- A no ? No . - No ?
( chuckles ) : No , not a no .
- No , not no ? - Uh , yes .
( chuckles )
Big yes to dinner .
Ooh . Um , a feast . A full feast , Master .
In fact , I 'm so glad you 're here .
Um , I was actually , um ... I was on my way to see you .
Oh , you were on your way .
Yes , but I had , um , too many bodies .
- Oh , you-you have bodies , huh ? - Yeah , too ... too many .
Well , uh , so many bodies , um , that I couldn 't carry them all .
- Uh , you should have seen it . - Mm . Mm-hmm .
The problem is my back has really been playing up .
Anyway , the-the plan is to rent a U-Haul , and that way ,
- I 'll be able to get all the bodies ... - Mm-hmm . Mm-hmm .
You know what ? It 's so silly , but you don 't have to worry ,
um , and I-I won 't bother you with my-my problems .
No , no .
Please , tell me all about your problems .
Tell me all about the gun-wielding criminals
who came after you for killing their men
because you were protecting so-called innocent people .
I 'm-I 'm sorry .
I 'm sorry , Master . I never meant to hurt you .
Hurt me ?
Are you actually suggesting
that anything you could do would hurt ...
me ? !
No . No , no , no , no , no . No , Master , I 'm sorry .
I didn 't mean ... I didn 't mean that .
No , no , it 's-it 's all right . It 's all right .
- Really ? - No , it 's ... Yeah .
Let me explain something to you , okay ?
- Okay . - I was wrong about you .
I should 've realized what you were capable of
when you were so eager to join me .
I-I don 't think I was eager .
I think that you caught me at a low moment
- and you maybe manipulated me , too . - No , no , no ,
- no , no ... - And you just caught me at a low moment
- and used some of your power ... - ... no , no , no , no , no , no , no !
I use my power for a lot of things ,
but I didn 't need to use it on you .
You were a lawyer who wanted to get rich
off a real estate deal .
You 're the one who used me !
You used my power because you 're a husk .
An empty void that nothing can fill .
The only thing that gave your life any meaning was my power .
The power you used to bring me victims
while you pretended to be one yourself .
( exhales heavily )
However , I 'm the real victim here !
I 'm the one you swore to protect !
And you ...
abandoned me !
No .
That 's not true .
Just like you abandoned
your wife and your daughter .
That 's not ... I didn 't ...
I didn 't abandon them .
Look into your own eyes , Renfield .
You 're the monster , Renfield , not me .
It 's you .
No . No .
That 's enough . That 's enough .
What ?
( sighs )
I will no longer tolerate abuse .
( laughing )
Stop laughing .
I deserve love .
I deserve happiness .
You deserve only suffering .
Um , oh . I know being undead , it 's a painful existence - -
it is - - and I empathize with your pain .
Oh , please . Illuminate me .
Let me learn from you .
I will find everyone you have ever loved ,
and I will drain them .
- I will reduce this ... this ... - S-Studio apartment ?
... studio apartment until it 's ash !
Uh ... uh ...
Affirmations , affirmations .
Uh , I 'm enough , and , um , I deserve some happiness .
There is some other stuff that I have to say .
Who put these ideas in your head ?
( sighs )
Of course .
( whooshing )
What ?
Shit .
You think Doug was murdered ?
I can 't say for sure , but I ...
I hope he was fucking murdered .
I hope he was torn to itty-bitty pieces and then ...
I shouldn 't be saying that to a cop , right ?
CAITLYN : Karla , margaritas are ready !
Caitlyn ! Oh , God . This ...
CAITLYN : Try this .
Are you Caitlyn Berggren ?
I can be anybody I want now .
That 's right . Yes , you can .
Did you file a missing persons report for Mitch Flaherty ?
- Maybe . - Are you Caitlyn ?
H-How do you two know each other ?
- Um , from this support group thing . - ( snickers )
Uh , for people addicted to assholes .
- ( chuckles ) - ( shushes )
- Assholes Anonymous . - ( Caitlyn shushing )
At the Livespring Church .
CAROL : I realized that I can identify healthy love .
I just don 't think I deserve it .
Um , and that 's partially the shame talking ,
but also the rash ...
Renfield ?
Can I get through one fucking share , please ?
Is , uh ... is everyone okay ?
- If that 's what you want to call it . - MARK : We 're all fine .
- What 's going on ? What 's going on ? - We , uh ...
We need to leave . Now .
I mean , where 's the rule that says we have to talk
about our feelings in a gym ? Come on , please .
Up . Up . Let 's go somewhere safe till morning .
Come on , up . Everybody , move . Come on .
Renfield , just take a deep breath .
We are all fine . I promise ...
Mark , we need to leave now .
- All right ... - ( door bangs open )
Hi . Uh , are you here for the meeting ?
Well , come on in .
No ! No ! No !
( electrical crackling )
♪ ♪
You can leave your top hat and cane by the door .
Renfield .
I 'm ... ( laughs )
feeling much better .
Don 't .
Would you like to introduce yourself to the group ?
I 'm the prince of Wallachia .
( laughs )
Some call me the Dark One .
Others , the Lord of Death .
( giggles )
However , to most ,
I am known simply as ...
- Renfield 's boss ! - ( snarling )
I am Dracula .
Okay . Obviously , we 're dealing with
a little bit more than just narcissism here .
Master .
Please .
I should never have forsaken you .
You could 've had everything .
I gave you the choice between
( echoes loudly ) : the power of a god
and the pathetic desperation of humanity .
Why ?
Why would you choose this ?
Because
that 's what I am .
Master , please .
These are good people .
Good . You 've finally brought me what I 've been asking for .
Let 's eat .
Please . Please . No .
No !
- ( hisses ) - ( screaming )
Please , Dracula !
( people screaming )
( whimpering )
( screams )
No .
Oh , no , no , no , no . I 'm sorry .
There are some experiences
worse than death , Renfield .
Such as spending the remaining years
of your miserable life
knowing all the depravity
you 've witnessed in the last century
will be nothing compared to the suffering
I 'm going to unleash on this world .
The world you chose over mine .
When I 'm finished , the entire human race ,
everyone you care about , will suffer .
Because you betrayed me .
( whooshing )
♪ ♪
- Holy shit . - Hands in the air .
( trembling breaths )
RENFIELD : I destroyed everything .
I 'll call it in .
RENFIELD : I thought I could save these people
by bringing Dracula all of their monsters ,
but what I 've really done is
deliver my monster right to them .
REBECCA : Did you call it in ?
Yeah , yeah , yeah .
( tires squealing )
( sirens wailing )
What the fuck ?
I 'm sorry , Rebecca .
BELLAFRANCESCA : It 's okay .
This is not about you , Miss Quincy .
It 's about him .
I need to find out what happened to Teddy
and punish those responsible .
You , of all people , should understand that .
Well , I was gonna take him to jail .
You all should come , too .
Look , Quincy , this is a big arrest you made .
I want to offer you a full promotion .
Right ? Better hours , better pay ,
better parking space - - in fact , Kyle 's parking space .
- Uh , hey . - Fuck you , Kyle !
Congratulations .
I know this is not exactly what you were hoping for ,
but success really is the best revenge .
♪ ♪
Okay .
( frantic chatter , shouting )
Fuck !
I want the whole city activated .
Find them .
OFFICER ( over radio ) : Attention , all officers .
Officer Rebecca Quincy is now a wanted fugitive .
She and her male accomplice are armed and extremely dangerous .
OFFICER 2 : Officer Rebecca Quincy
and one unknown assailant .
Proceed with deadly force .
( groaning , muttering )
Wait , wait , wait , wait .
Wait , wait , wait , wait , wait , wait , wait .
Fuck , fuck , fuck . Wait , wait , wait , wait .
Wait . No , no , no , no , no .
( panting )
This crime family of yours ,
would it enjoy witnessing
the beheading of its enemies
and the impalement of all who oppose it ?
That 's-that 's ... that 's , like , our ...
that 's , like , our whole thing , man .
And can the family raise me soldiers ?
We can ... I can make a couple calls , yeah .
Whatever pain Renfield caused you ,
I will return 10,000-fold .
I will unleash an army of death
whilst warming my skin
next to mountains of burning corpses .
How does that sound to you ?
( Teddy grunts )
It sounds like you got to meet my mom .
( laughing )
( chuckles nervously )
Are you happy , or are you gonna fuck me up ?
( both yell )
( laughing continues )
- ( rustling nearby ) - ( soft grunting )
( music playing quietly )
How are you feeling ?
Hope you 're hungry .
It 's okay .
It 's okay , your gun and phone are on the side right there .
I 'm just gonna ... gonna set these down right here .
There we go .
- Where am I ? - My place .
It 's not an abduction .
In fact , uh , you know , I 'm very much still in your custody .
Mind if I sit ?
( sighs )
Snickerdoodle ?
I don 't want your murder cookies .
They 're just regular cookies .
Well , I don 't know what " regular cookies " means
to a murderer .
Um , I don 't really know that , either .
Ooh . Careful .
- You should just rest up . - Oh . Okay .
- You okay ? - Yes .
Give me the ... give me the murder cookie .
- Oh , yeah . - Just not the one that looks like shit .
RENFIELD : I don 't know which one you think looks like shit .
Thank you .
Listen , I feel like I should give you an explanation .
No explanation necessary .
I don 't want you to think of me as some kind of ... murderer ,
when it 's really much more nuanced than that .
You know , if you just hear me out for a second ,
then you 'll understand I 'm ... I 'm not such a bad guy .
I don 't give a shit what kind of guy you are .
Okay , there 's no need to be mean .
Excuse me ?
I saved your life . Twice .
I 'm not saying we need to be friends , but you 're in
a lot of shit right now , and there 's a very good chance
I might be the only person you can actually trust .
The fact that you are the only person that I can trust
just proves that I am monumentally fucked .
Well , maybe you 're fucked because of
- your unresolved anger . - What ? !
I 'm no psychologist , but I 've been to a couple of meetings ...
Oh , you 've-you 've been to some meetings ? Yeah ?
Where the people come in , they 're like , " Oh , hi .
How you doing ? " Drink some coffee ,
then get brutally fucking murdered ?
Those meetings ?
Uh , yes . Those meetings .
You know what ?
I am angry .
I graduated top of my class ,
and I 'm still working DUI checkpoints
in a town with daiquiri drive-throughs .
I bust my ass for a city that is corrupt
and lets the people that killed my father
get away with anything they want to do .
But unlike you , I can 't go and take out my anger
by killing every asshole on the street who I think deserves it .
I 'm sorry . That sounds ...
painful and , um ...
I 'm not taking out my anger , if you 'd let me explain .
Please .
Okay .
By all means .
( clears throat )
I work for Dracula .
What ?
Dracula .
Dracula ?
- Dracula . - Count Dracula ?
No , no . President Dracula .
Yes , of co ... Yes . Sorry .
Count Dracula . I 'm ... I 'm his familiar .
I-I ... you know , I tend to his needs ,
including care , feeding , uh , you know ,
anything especially during the daylight hours .
Like , you get Dracula people to eat ?
I do other stuff , too .
Like what ? Wash his cape ?
No .
It 's dry-clean only .
( sighs ) My God .
I cannot believe I bought into your bullshit .
You 're not a hero .
You 're not even a villain .
You 're just a guy that kills random people .
( cell phone vibrating )
What ?
Rebecca , you were right .
I ran that pen through Interpol .
This is beyond the Lobos .
Whoever 's responsible for those disappearances
has been linked to cases all over the world
going back decades .
If this is the same guy , he 's probably 70 or 80 years old
and he might be the most prolific serial killer
the world has ever known .
So , where are you ?
Where am I ? Um ...
I 'm-I 'm at his ... I 'm at his place .
But-but it 's-it 's okay because he 's-he 's in ...
- he 's in my custody . - What ?
And he made me some cookies .
You didn 't eat the cookies , did you ?
No . I don 't eat the cookies of strange men .
Okay . Well , I 'm gonna head over there with my team .
No , no , no . Don 't . I need to get him to you .
The Lobos are after him , too .
I don 't know who we can trust .
Meet me at Café Du Monde in 20 minutes .
Okay , just ... please be careful , Rebecca .
You , too .
♪ ♪
- ( sirens blaring ) - ( engines revving )
( tires squealing )
Oh , shit .
REBECCA : Go , go .
OFFICER ( over radio ) : All units , you have a green light .
Commence attack .
( siren blaring )
We need to find a bug . Now .
( indistinct chatter )
REBECCA : Why ?
Their life force gives me power .
Their life force gives you power ?
Yes . It 's confusing , but trust me , it works .
Any second now , a shit ton of guys
are coming up those stairs , and if you want me to do
what I did at the restaurant , we need to find a bug now .
- You two , with me . - Go , go , go .
Come on . A juicy spider , anything .
Yes !
Give me that !
( grunting )
You 're a bad man , Mr. Renfield !
Yeah , well ...
Sometimes that comes in handy .
( " Superdeadfriends " by Yungblud playing )
♪ I want to live in a new dimension ♪
♪ Take a rocket ship without no suspension ♪
♪ I want to live in a world where I ♪
♪ Can be who I am without having to try ♪
♪ Mum , Dad , let me breathe ♪
♪ Let me be free to come off my feet ♪
♪ When you 're making a baby in missionary ♪
♪ Be prepared to accept them for what they 're gonna be ♪
♪ ♪
( groans )
- Ooh . - That son of a bitch can fly ?
♪ Super dead kids with super dead friends ♪
♪ You 're inside my head , you 're inside my head ♪
♪ We got something left , yeah , yeah ♪
♪ Each other ... ♪
( screaming )
- Oh , shit ! - Whoa .
- Oh , shit ! - Oh , shit .
♪ Super dead kids with super dead friends ♪
♪ We got something left ♪
♪ Yeah , yeah , each other ♪
( yelling )
♪ I got a travel ban from this planet ♪
♪ They locked me in a room with a man with no manners ♪
♪ We don 't care if you 're Black or you 're white ♪
♪ Asian or sexually intertwined ♪
♪ It 's time to take a look at the world through our eyes ♪
♪ If you stick around , you may like what you find ♪
♪ Take two from me and you start to divide ♪
♪ It 'll give you all the energy ♪
♪ Times it by five ♪
( groans )
( screaming )
♪ ' Cause they 'll never know where you were coming from ♪
♪ Super dead kids with super dead friends ♪
♪ You 're inside my head , you 're inside my head ♪
♪ We got something left , yeah , yeah , each other ♪
♪ Super dead kids with super dead friends ♪
♪ You 're inside my head , you 're inside my head . ♪
- ( song ends ) - ( panting )
♪ ♪
( grunts )
( panting )
You know when something crazy happens
and someone 's like ,
" I 'm so sorry you had to see that " ?
- Mm . - And the other person 's like ,
" It 's okay , I 've seen way worse " ?
Yeah .
Everything I saw you do today is gonna be my " way worse . "
This shit 's gotten completely out of control .
And for what ? Teddy ?
He 's a freaking idiot .
I 'm sorry , Bella , but I 'm out .
Get the fuck out my way .
This whole family is fucking nuts .
Oh , hey . I was just talking about ...
- ( thump , slashing ) - ( screams )
Looks like he 's back in .
Son .
( chuckling ) : Oh , Mom .
Where have you been ?
Oh , I 've been getting my hands real fucking dirty .
Come here . I got to show you someone .
♪ ♪
Right there . Put it down right there .
Right in front of the head .
It 's fucking Dracula !
It 's the real fucking Dracula !
Fuck , man !
He wants to take over the world with us .
Hello , Mr. Dracula .
Or should I say Prince Dracula ?
Enchantée .
The pleasure is all mine .
We have much to discuss .
Oh .
Okay .
REBECCA : God , I hope my sister gets here soon .
There 's a lot of heat on us .
RENFIELD : I took my family to a place like this in London
the morning I left for Dracula 's castle .
You had a family ?
I did .
Um , it was a ... a long time ago .
A really long time ago .
Yeah , I 'm older than I look .
That 's Lilian . She was five then .
I thought going to Europe
to make some big deal with a count
would give us the life we deserved .
Or , um ...
what I thought I deserved .
I let them down in so many ways .
You know , that 's his greatest power .
He looks into your eyes and finds
what you think you need to make your life whole .
Your ... your dreams and your desires
and your ... greed .
Your shame .
I blamed him for forcing me to abandon my family ,
but that ... that 's not true .
I ...
I wanted all those things , and I chose to follow him .
I 'm not a victim . I 'm ...
I made all those mistakes on my own .
Look , I don 't think you 're such a bad guy .
Life throws a lot of shit at you ,
but sometimes you fall under the thrall
of a vampire for a few decades ,
and sometimes you call your sister an unbearable twat
at Grandma 's birthday party .
( chuckles softly )
You should make things right with your sister while you can .
Hmm ?
Speaking of .
I 'm gonna call her .
DRACULA : Renfield . It 's so wonderful
that you have finally found someone
who does inspire you to grow as a person .
Hey , where are you ?
DRACULA : I have found some people
who will unleash my potential as well .
They understand this world
for what it is and what it needs .
BELLAFRANCESCA ( over phone ) : Hello , Rebecca .
Looking for someone ?
Where 's my sister ?
I offered you so much , Rebecca ,
but you put your faith in such fragile institutions
instead of something far more enduring .
We 've got your sister .
She doesn 't have much time .
Rebecca , where are you going ?
- To get my sister . - Rebecca , you don 't understand .
It 's not just the Lobos . It 's ...
Dracula is with them .
- Fine . I 'll go myself . - Look , please .
I tried to stand up to him ,
and he killed people I cared about .
I can 't let that happen again .
You want to be a hero , Renfield ?
You have to risk everything .
And as someone that cares about you ,
you 're never really gonna be free until you face him .
You care about me ?
Is that what it takes to get you in the car ?
All right , if we 're gonna do this ,
we need to prepare , and we need to do it before sunset .
I 'm ready to do it before lunch .
Okay .
REBECCA : Let 's face it , they know we 're coming ,
so let 's go in style .
( engine revving , tires squealing )
Yeah , just guns won 't be enough .
I 'm gonna need bugs - - lots of bugs - -
wooden stakes ,
uh , crucifixes ,
and , uh , maybe a protection circle .
What the fuck is a protection circle ?
It 's a circle made of powder that - -
it-it traps demons if you say the right ,
- uh , Latin stuff . - Forget it .
♪ Na , na-na-na , na-na-na , na-na , na-na ♪
♪ Na , na-na-na , na-na-na ... ♪
Oh , once it 's dark , it 'll be too late .
( munching loudly )
Can you maybe save that for later ?
Oh , sorry .
- It 's all in ... - Is it in my teeth ?
It is in every tooth .
- ♪ Dress like a sleeper cell ♪ - ♪ Na , na-na-na , na-na-na ♪
♪ I 'd rather go to hell ♪
♪ Pull this pin , let this world explode . ♪
Uh ...
No matter what happens in there , ju ...
Make sure you save your sister .
( sighs )
♪ ♪
Must be nice ...
not needing to be invited in .
Wait a second . Wait a second . Don 't I know you ?
Because you look so ...
( snorts )
... familiar .
♪ ♪
( yelling , grunting )
( gunshot )
( screams )
( yells )
( laughing )
Afternoon , Officer .
Shit . I 'm out .
You think I need guns to fuck you up ?
Let 's do this . What the fuck ?
( grunting )
Fuck !
( grunting and groaning )
You should 've taken my offer when you had the chance .
Now the only choice you 're gonna get
is which one of your limbs I 'm gonna tear off first !
Go !
No !
( groaning )
Oh , this must drive you crazy - - him choosing me over you .
I don 't really have strong feelings about it .
I 'm clearly the yin to your yang .
We 've barely met twice .
You patronizing piece of shit !
Oh , my goodness .
You almost scared me .
Where 's my sister ?
Oh , that .
One moment , please .
I need to set the mood first .
( trembling breaths )
- Hello , Rebecca . - ( gasps )
Don 't worry .
I won 't hurt you .
It 's nice to finally meet you .
I can only imagine what you might have heard about me
from poor Renfield .
Besides making him bring you people to eat ?
( chuckling ) : Well , we did have a complicated relationship .
However , when I saw you through his eyes ,
I knew I had to make things right .
Having Dracula powers is fucking amazing .
Stop saying " Dracula powers . "
Fine . What do you call it ?
It 's a curse .
God , you 're such a fucking drama queen .
Would you please listen ?
They come with a cost , okay ?
You 'll become his slave .
See , that 's where you 're wrong , because Master told me ...
Shit .
Mm-hmm .
For half a millennium , I 've seen only weakness
in the hearts of men .
And then I looked into yours .
Renfield used only the smallest taste of my power
to do what he thought was good .
Imagine what I could do , Rebecca , with you by my side .
We could bring the justice you seek
to those who 've escaped it for too long .
( groans )
- And I can heal your sister . - ( gasps )
My blood will bring her back .
No .
DRACULA : Say the word , Rebecca ,
and I will undo what the Lobos have done .
All I ask in exchange ...
( sniffling )
... is for you
to join me .
No , don 't listen to him .
He said the same shit to me .
Can you save her ?
Yes .
( yells )
TEDDY : What did he call you again ?
An empty fucking husk ?
See , that ... that is why
Dracula and I work so well together .
I 'm a full husk ,
full of everything you 're not .
Strength , power , loyalty !
( groaning )
DRACULA : Her time is running out .
Oh , join me .
Don 't .
I told you , this is what he does .
REBECCA : So what ?
I lost my dad .
I can 't lose my sister .
And if he can give her back to me
I don 't care if I lose myself .
You were wrong about him .
He 's not a monster .
He wants to be better , like you .
Maybe I can help .
In all the darkness , I can find the light .
( chuckling softly )
Shit .
( switch clicking )
( hisses )
( screaming )
( button beeping )
( bats squeaking )
( grunts )
( metal clinking )
( trembling breaths )
( electrical buzzing )
( wings fluttering )
( rustling nearby )
DRACULA : That was impressive .
I can see what Renfield saw ...
in you .
( snarls )
Now he 'll see it go into me .
( hisses )
( grunts )
Congratulations .
You shot my foot .
Your foot still bleeds .
( hissing )
Die !
( yells )
( screams ) No ! Oh , no !
( shouting )
( laughing )
You can 't take my teeth .
You see , there will always be people like you .
There are far more Renfields in this world
than there are Rebeccas .
RENFIELD : He 's right .
There are millions of people like me .
GROUP : I am enough ...
RENFIELD : And they 're all
trying to figure out
how to overcome their destructive relationships .
Always remember , you 're the one with the real power .
RENFIELD : Millions of codependent people .
I am the dark poetry in the hearts of all mankind .
- ( laughing ) - RENFIELD : Millions of people
just like me .
All you got to do is take it back .
Do you know what you are ?
Yes , I do .
- I 'm Robert ... - ( groaning )
Montague Renfield ,
and I 'm a codependent .
♪ ♪
You 're right . You didn 't have to use your power
to make me your servant ,
because I gave all my power to you .
And I can take it back .
I am enough !
And I have enough !
And I am capable of change !
( panting )
Because I love myself .
- ( groans ) - I 'm taking ...
full charge of my life today !
Look into my eyes , Dracula .
( whimpering )
Full power , motherfucker .
( gasps )
( yells )
Holy shit , it worked .
RENFIELD : Is that a protection circle ?
I got the instructions off a Wiccan Tumblr .
Oh . And-and that ?
- Cocaine . - Really ?
Yeah . I guess any kind of powder works
as long as you say the right magic words .
Wow . ( chuckles ) Thank you , Wiccan Tumblr .
( Dracula grunting )
So , um , what do we do now ?
( " Yesterday , Tomorrow Today " by David Wilkins playing )
♪ I wake up each morning ♪
♪ With your sweet kiss on my mind ♪
♪ The early morning sun shining through ♪
Any last wishes ?
I wish to spend a season in hell ,
where all the amusing people are .
Hail Satan !
♪ I see your face in every ... ♪
RENFIELD : Yes , I know this looks extreme ,
and maybe a little fun ,
but to our defense , there is so much
folklore out there about how to actually kill a vampire ,
it gets confusing .
You know , I 've personally seen him come back
from some crazy shit , so why not try everything ?
You know , I 'm not even 100 % sure this will kill him ,
but I do know it will take him a long , long time
to come back from .
♪ You 're my yesterday , tomorrow and today . ♪
( song ends )
REBECCA : You were right .
Success is the best revenge .
Touché , ma chérie .
Au revoir , bitch .
Hey . You okay ?
Renfield said you guys gave me some ...
( chuckling ) : Dracula blood ?
Oh , no , no . It 's a euphemism for , uh ...
it 's an ... it 's an ... like , an herbal remedy .
Okay . So , do you think they carry it at GNC ?
Yeah . Yeah , I th-think so .
( laughs )
I love you , Kate .
So ...
There 's only one thing left to do .
You know ...
I 've got to pay for what I 've done .
I don 't want you to go somewhere just to punish yourself .
You belong out in the world .
People have a lot to learn from a person like you .
Like what ?
It 's never too late to be a hero .
Hmm .
RENFIELD : I was lost in a world of darkness
for a very long time ,
but with all of your help ,
I , um ...
I found a way out .
Without you , I would never have learned that
I could save myself .
And thank you for using Dracula blood
to bring us all back to life .
- ( light laughter , murmuring ) - You know , if it ...
if it wasn 't for you , uh , none of us
would have learned what it 's like
to come back from the other side ,
having seen things
that you can 't unsee .
And know things
that you can 't unknow .
( chuckles ) Okay .
Fantastic meeting today , guys .
- Truly . - ( others murmuring )
( " I 'm Free " by The Soup Dragons playing )
I hope he 's okay .
- He 'll be all right . - Hmm .
RENFIELD : My name is Robert Montague Renfield ,
and I 'm a codependent .
But I no longer feel like a victim ,
because I 've finally faced my demons .
You might also say I chopped my demons up
into tiny little pieces , encased them in concrete
and flushed them down the drain .
And if I can find the power to do that ,
then maybe everyone can .
( chuckles ) Metaphorically speaking .
♪ I 'm free to do what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ I said I 'm free to do what I want ♪
♪ I say love me , hold me ♪
♪ Love me , hold me ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free ♪
- ♪ I say love me ♪ - ♪ Love me forever ♪
- ♪ Hold me ♪ - ♪ And love will never die ♪
♪ Love me , hold me ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free ♪
♪ Do you hear what the man say ? ♪
♪ These are the words me hear from my granddaddy , come ♪
♪ These are the words me hear from my granddaddy ♪
♪ He would say nothing in this world ♪
♪ Like when a man know he free ♪
♪ Free from the lockup , me say free from the debt ♪
♪ Free like a butterfly , free like a bee ♪
♪ These are the words me hear from my granddaddy ♪
♪ Said it 's nice to be free , nice to be free ♪
♪ Free from the lockup , me say free from the debt ♪
♪ Don 't be afraid of your freedom ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free to do what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ I 'm a new creation ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free ♪
♪ To do what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ Don 't be afraid of your freedom ♪
♪ I said I 'm free to do what I want ♪
♪ To be what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ I said I 'm free to be who I choose ♪
♪ To get my booze ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free ♪
♪ To do what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ I 'm free ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free ♪
♪ To do what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ I 'm free ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free to do what I want ♪
♪ Any old time ♪
♪ I 'm free ♪
♪ ' Cause I 'm free . ♪
( song ends )
♪ ♪
( music fades )